[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "In terms of the veracity of Barack Obama's story?", "question_tokens": ["In", "terms", "of", "the", "veracity", "of", "Barack", "Obama", "'s", "story", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Thanks for asking it that way.", "answer_tokens": ["Thanks", "for", "asking", "it", "that", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How much should we factor that in to perhaps some of the things you've unearthed that aren't quite right?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "should", "we", "factor", "that", "in", "to", "perhaps", "some", "of", "the", "things", "you", "'ve", "unearthed", "that", "are", "n't", "quite", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "TO", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "He did say that in his introduction to his book.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "did", "say", "that", "in", "his", "introduction", "to", "his", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "To retrain is the narrative?", "question_tokens": ["To", "retrain", "is", "the", "narrative", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Well, he says he only changed the narrative -- used composite characters and compressed chronology in order to make the story smoother but in fact he did it for other reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "says", "he", "only", "changed", "the", "narrative", "--", "used", "composite", "characters", "and", "compressed", "chronology", "in", "order", "to", "make", "the", "story", "smoother", "but", "in", "fact", "he", "did", "it", "for", "other", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "What is the real Barack Obama like from what you discovered from 350 separate interviews with people who knew him very well?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "real", "Barack", "Obama", "like", "from", "what", "you", "discovered", "from", "350", "separate", "interviews", "with", "people", "who", "knew", "him", "very", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "He's introspective, he's cautious, he's what I call a partisan observer in his own life.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "introspective", ",", "he", "'s", "cautious", ",", "he", "'s", "what", "I", "call", "a", "partisan", "observer", "in", "his", "own", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Did you find him basically an honest man?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "find", "him", "basically", "an", "honest", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Would you think he's got a bit of a free pass on that to some degree?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "got", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "free", "pass", "on", "that", "to", "some", "degree", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, it's a different generation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "different", "generation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "How did you find the comparison between President Obama and President Clinton, having now immersed yourself in their lives?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "find", "the", "comparison", "between", "President", "Obama", "and", "President", "Clinton", ",", "having", "now", "immersed", "yourself", "in", "their", "lives", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "If you were thinking about whether to vote for him or not in November, what is the one thing where you thought, you know what, that isn't good?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "thinking", "about", "whether", "to", "vote", "for", "him", "or", "not", "in", "November", ",", "what", "is", "the", "one", "thing", "where", "you", "thought", ",", "you", "know", "what", ",", "that", "is", "n't", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Well, I didn't see anything venal.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "see", "anything", "venal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2004"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "RB", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "A timidity?", "question_tokens": ["A", "timidity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, and a little bit -- you know, it's interesting because he always dismissed his mother as being naive but he came into the presidency with a little bit of naivete in terms of thinking that that grand speech he gave in 2004 bringing the whole country together, which in my book, in my interview, he said that he couldn't find a reason to exist if not for that universality.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "a", "little", "bit", "--", "you", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "because", "he", "always", "dismissed", "his", "mother", "as", "being", "naive", "but", "he", "came", "into", "the", "presidency", "with", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "naivete", "in", "terms", "of", "thinking", "that", "that", "grand", "speech", "he", "gave", "in", "2004", "bringing", "the", "whole", "country", "together", ",", "which", "in", "my", "book", ",", "in", "my", "interview", ",", "he", "said", "that", "he", "could", "n't", "find", "a", "reason", "to", "exist", "if", "not", "for", "that", "universality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "NN", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 167, "question": "-- did you see that now in the presidency?", "question_tokens": ["--", "did", "you", "see", "that", "now", "in", "the", "presidency", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "With an occasional bold action which is also what everybody saw --", "answer_tokens": ["With", "an", "occasional", "bold", "action", "which", "is", "also", "what", "everybody", "saw", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "Conversely, what are the big positives that you found are consistent then to what he is now?", "question_tokens": ["Conversely", ",", "what", "are", "the", "big", "positives", "that", "you", "found", "are", "consistent", "then", "to", "what", "he", "is", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBP", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "What I've found that's positive largely is that he is a human being who's growing and learning.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "I", "'ve", "found", "that", "'s", "positive", "largely", "is", "that", "he", "is", "a", "human", "being", "who", "'s", "growing", "and", "learning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "Piers, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Yes, it's good to talk to you again.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "good", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Shellie"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ",", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "What is your reaction to these transcripts and to the prosecution's position over them?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "these", "transcripts", "and", "to", "the", "prosecution", "'s", "position", "over", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Well, they are certainly significant to the one minor issue, if you will, of whether or not Shellie new about the amount of money that was in the accounts because clearly they show that she did.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "are", "certainly", "significant", "to", "the", "one", "minor", "issue", ",", "if", "you", "will", ",", "of", "whether", "or", "not", "Shellie", "new", "about", "the", "amount", "of", "money", "that", "was", "in", "the", "accounts", "because", "clearly", "they", "show", "that", "she", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$155"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "OK, so total everything, how much are we looking at?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "so", "total", "everything", ",", "how", "much", "are", "we", "looking", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Like $155.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "$", "155", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$155", "$155,000"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "$", "CD", "WRB", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "$", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "I mean is it -- is the reality that they do have hundreds of thousands of dollars?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "is", "it", "--", "is", "the", "reality", "that", "they", "do", "have", "hundreds", "of", "thousands", "of", "dollars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "There's no question that they were talking in this sort of simplistic kind of code where they were talking about $155 when, without question, they were talking about $155,000.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "question", "that", "they", "were", "talking", "in", "this", "sort", "of", "simplistic", "kind", "of", "code", "where", "they", "were", "talking", "about", "$", "155", "when", ",", "without", "question", ",", "they", "were", "talking", "about", "$", "155,000", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["hundreds of thousands of dollars"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "So I mean if you were putting a prosecutorial hat on, rather your current defense hat, you can see why the prosecution would be pretty agitated, can you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "mean", "if", "you", "were", "putting", "a", "prosecutorial", "hat", "on", ",", "rather", "your", "current", "defense", "hat", ",", "you", "can", "see", "why", "the", "prosecution", "would", "be", "pretty", "agitated", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "No question, they did not tell a complete truth to the judge.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "question", ",", "they", "did", "not", "tell", "a", "complete", "truth", "to", "the", "judge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "I mean it doesn't help you, to be brutally frank, does it not, that they appear to have lied in this, because when it comes to George Zimmerman defending himself and saying X, Y, Z, about what happened with Trayvon Martin, there will be critics now, understandably, saying, why should we believe you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "it", "does", "n't", "help", "you", ",", "to", "be", "brutally", "frank", ",", "does", "it", "not", ",", "that", "they", "appear", "to", "have", "lied", "in", "this", ",", "because", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "George", "Zimmerman", "defending", "himself", "and", "saying", "X", ",", "Y", ",", "Z", ",", "about", "what", "happened", "with", "Trayvon", "Martin", ",", "there", "will", "be", "critics", "now", ",", "understandably", ",", "saying", ",", "why", "should", "we", "believe", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Absolutely true.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "-- that you can believe now what George Zimmerman has told you about, as you say, the more serious issue of what happened that night with Trayvon Martin?", "question_tokens": ["--", "that", "you", "can", "believe", "now", "what", "George", "Zimmerman", "has", "told", "you", "about", ",", "as", "you", "say", ",", "the", "more", "serious", "issue", "of", "what", "happened", "that", "night", "with", "Trayvon", "Martin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "I would tell you that as we know the conversation between client and lawyer are so privileged, but I will tell you this, that I had never asked him a question about that fund because I wasn't aware of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "tell", "you", "that", "as", "we", "know", "the", "conversation", "between", "client", "and", "lawyer", "are", "so", "privileged", ",", "but", "I", "will", "tell", "you", "this", ",", "that", "I", "had", "never", "asked", "him", "a", "question", "about", "that", "fund", "because", "I", "was", "n't", "aware", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"], "PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Lester", "George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "That he could just be now in jail for possibly up to two years before this come to trial?", "question_tokens": ["That", "he", "could", "just", "be", "now", "in", "jail", "for", "possibly", "up", "to", "two", "years", "before", "this", "come", "to", "trial", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Judge Lester put his neck out for George Zimmerman.", "answer_tokens": ["Judge", "Lester", "put", "his", "neck", "out", "for", "George", "Zimmerman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What was your reaction when you saw the transcript?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "you", "saw", "the", "transcript", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, Piers, they truly take this very, very seriously.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "they", "truly", "take", "this", "very", ",", "very", "seriously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Are you concerned about serious threats to your life?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "serious", "threats", "to", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "This is what I do for a living.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "what", "I", "do", "for", "a", "living", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "How would you describe their relationship?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "their", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "To the extent that I know about, they are good.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "the", "extent", "that", "I", "know", "about", ",", "they", "are", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "What do you think of that strategy by the defense?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "strategy", "by", "the", "defense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "It may be the one strategy they have.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "may", "be", "the", "one", "strategy", "they", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How credible have you found the witnesses so far?", "question_tokens": ["How", "credible", "have", "you", "found", "the", "witnesses", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "The witnesses for the prosecution I found them to be very credible.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "witnesses", "for", "the", "prosecution", "I", "found", "them", "to", "be", "very", "credible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "How relevant do you think that could be?", "question_tokens": ["How", "relevant", "do", "you", "think", "that", "could", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I think it's very relevant.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "relevant", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Would you, if you were defending Jerry Sandusky, risk him on the stand?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", ",", "if", "you", "were", "defending", "Jerry", "Sandusky", ",", "risk", "him", "on", "the", "stand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "These are very difficult cases generically to have a client or defendant testifying, because there are so many land mines that are going to occur with the numerous witness who testified.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "very", "difficult", "cases", "generically", "to", "have", "a", "client", "or", "defendant", "testifying", ",", "because", "there", "are", "so", "many", "land", "mines", "that", "are", "going", "to", "occur", "with", "the", "numerous", "witness", "who", "testified", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jerry Sandusky"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Have you forgiven in your mind the policeman that did what they did to you?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "forgiven", "in", "your", "mind", "the", "policeman", "that", "did", "what", "they", "did", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Oh yes, I have forgiven them, because America has forgiven me for so many things And gave me so many chances.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "I", "have", "forgiven", "them", ",", "because", "America", "has", "forgiven", "me", "for", "so", "many", "things", "And", "gave", "me", "so", "many", "chances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "In many ways, he was this iconic symbol, wasn't he, for race in modern America?", "question_tokens": ["In", "many", "ways", ",", "he", "was", "this", "iconic", "symbol", ",", "was", "n't", "he", ",", "for", "race", "in", "modern", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Not only an iconic symbol, but I think he actually, unbeknownst to him when he was doing it -- I think he changed this city.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "only", "an", "iconic", "symbol", ",", "but", "I", "think", "he", "actually", ",", "unbeknownst", "to", "him", "when", "he", "was", "doing", "it", "--", "I", "think", "he", "changed", "this", "city", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "Do you believe that in the end it will be seen as a race case, that case, the Trayvon Martin killing?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "in", "the", "end", "it", "will", "be", "seen", "as", "a", "race", "case", ",", "that", "case", ",", "the", "Trayvon", "Martin", "killing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Well, I think in this country, it's hard to escape race whenever you have a child who's killed by a man who is not an African- American.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "in", "this", "country", ",", "it", "'s", "hard", "to", "escape", "race", "whenever", "you", "have", "a", "child", "who", "'s", "killed", "by", "a", "man", "who", "is", "not", "an", "African-", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon Martin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rodney"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "How much was it affected by what happened that day, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "was", "it", "affected", "by", "what", "happened", "that", "day", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "You know, I felt bad for Rodney.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "felt", "bad", "for", "Rodney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "I believe you have an announcement for us?", "question_tokens": ["I", "believe", "you", "have", "an", "announcement", "for", "us", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "I know that you've just been itching for a chance to go back, but do it in a new way, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "know", "that", "you", "'ve", "just", "been", "itching", "for", "a", "chance", "to", "go", "back", ",", "but", "do", "it", "in", "a", "new", "way", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 552, "question": "When did it all start to happen?", "question_tokens": ["When", "did", "it", "all", "start", "to", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, I actually went to CBS about two years ago and told them that I wanted to come home.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "went", "to", "CBS", "about", "two", "years", "ago", "and", "told", "them", "that", "I", "wanted", "to", "come", "home", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What is the secret to you avoiding the aging process?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "secret", "to", "you", "avoiding", "the", "aging", "process", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I drink my own urine.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "drink", "my", "own", "urine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2013", "fall"]}, "docId": "120618pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "When will you hit the airwaves?", "question_tokens": ["When", "will", "you", "hit", "the", "airwaves", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I will hit in 2013, the fall.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "hit", "in", "2013", ",", "the", "fall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]